BELOUSHKO STEPAN | БЕЛОУШКО СТЕПАН

+375 33 318-09-89: Telegram ◊ Minsk, Belarus

StepanIgorevich@hotmail.com https://github.com/Lasagnya

ABOUT ME

Hello!

I'm a Software Engineer with 1 year of experience in Java, seeking full-time Java Developer roles.

I am hardworking, communicative, willing to take on any task to develop my skills. I'm a workaholic, that's me. Has got along well in any teams before, so we'll be friends:) Any suggestions are welcome!

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Software Engineer, Belarussian State University, FAMI

2020 - 2024

Self-education of Java at books, video courses, pet projects.

SKILLS

Technical Skills - Java, Spring Framework (Core/AOP/REST/MVC/Data/Security), Hibernate

- REST, HTTP, SQL, Kafka, Redis, Git, Docker, patterns

- C++, Python, HTML

Soft Skills Perseverance, persevere in difficult situations, sociability, willingness to learn

Language skills English B1, French A1

EXPERIENCE

DeveloperJun 2022 - Sep 2022EpamMinsk, Belarus

- Developed knowledge of algorithms, Java language, studied Spring Core, MVC, Data JPA.
- Also learnt how to work with Docker. Wrote unit and integration tests. This all gave me a good boost in my subsequent studies.

DeveloperBeSmart
Dec 2023 - March 2024

Minsk, Belarus

- Banking sector, Developed REST API of the bank for making payments, using Spring Security and authentication through IWT
- Achieved understanding of building REST API, bank transfer schemes.

PROJECTS

Banking. REST API and console application for a bank with Spring Boot include Security, PostgreSQL. Transactions are secured with multithreading. The code contains documentation in JavaDoc format. (Link)

Library. CRUD web application for digital book registration. Also interacts with Banking for penalty charges through JSON. (Link)

ОБО МНЕ

Привет!

Я инженер-программист с 1 годом опыта работы в Java, ищу работу Java-разработчика на полный рабочий день.

Я трудолюбивый, общительный, готов взяться за любую задачу для развития своих навыков. Уйти с головой в работу - это про меня. Раньше хорошо ладил в любых коллективах, так что быстро вольюсь в команду :) Буду рад любым предложениям!

ОБУЧЕНИЕ

Бакалавреат, математик-программист, Белорусский государственный университет, ФПМИ

2020 - 2024

Самообучение Java по книгам, видео курсам, собственным проектам.

НАВЫКИ

Technical Skills

- Java, Spring Framework (Core/AOP/REST/MVC/Data/Security), Hibernate
- REST, HTTP, SQL, Kafka, Redis, Git, Docker, patterns
- C++, Python, HTML

Soft Skills

Настойчивость, упорство в трудных ситуациях, общительность, готовность к обучению

Language skills English B1, French A1

ОПЫТ

Epam

Developer

Июнь 2022 - Сентябрь 2022 Минск, Беларусь

- Развивал знания алгоритмов, языка Java, изучал Spring Core, MVC, Data JPA.
 - Также научился работать с Docker. Писал unit и integration тесты. Все это дало мне хороший толчок в дальнейшей учебе.

Developer

Декабрь 2023 - Март 2024

BeSmart

Минск, Беларусь

- Банковский сектор, разрабатывал REST API банка для осуществления транзакций, используя Spring Security и аутентификацию через JWT.
- Научился строить REST API, схему банковских переводов.

ПРОЕКТЫ

Banking. REST API и консольное приложение для банка со Spring Boot, использую Security, PostgreSQL. Транзакции защищены для работы в многопоточном режиме. Код содержит документацию в формате JavaDoc. (Link)

Library. CRUD веб-приложение для цифровой регистрации книг. Также взаимодействует с банковской системой для начисления штрафов через JSON. (Link)